puzzles.com 2009-11-07

# Puzzles.COM - Our Privacy Policy

|  |   
---|---|---  
|   Home / |   
|  |   
| 9 Quetions About Our Privacy Policy |   
|  |   
|  |   
|  What types of information are Puzzles.COM and ThinkFun collecting, and how are they collecting it? |   
|  |   
|  What Are Cookies, and How Does Puzzles.COM/ThinkFun Use Them? |   
|  |   
|  How does Puzzles.COM use the personally identifiable information that has been collected? |   
|  |   
|  Do Puzzles.COM or ThinkFun share information with companies or other organizations? |   
|  |   
|  What choices do I have about Puzzles.COM and ThinkFun collecting, using, and sharing my information? |   
|  |   
|  What type of security do Puzzles.COM and ThinkFun provide? |   
|  |   
|  How can I access my account information? |   
|  |   
|  How do parents access information about their kids? |   
|  |   
|  Whom do I contact with questions or concerns about this privacy policy? |   
|  |   
|  |   
|  What types of information are Puzzles.COM and ThinkFun collecting, and how are they collecting it? |   
|  The majority of products and services on our sites are offered without our collecting any personally identifiable information from you. You can surf our site and view much of our content anonymously.

Information You Provide  
There are a few activities on our site where the collection of personally identifiable information is necessary. Those activities include things like joining the PuzzleCLUB, making a purchase, or contacting us. When personally identifiable information is collected, you will know because you will have to fill out a form. For most activities, we collect only your name and e-mail address. When you make a purchase, we also collect your street and billing addresses, your phone number, and credit card information. By law, we are not allowed to collect more information from children than is reasonably necessary for participation in an activity. 

Information Collected from You with Technology  
Puzzles.COM and ThinkFun collect some information about you using technology, so it may not be readily apparent to you that it is being collected. For instance, when you come to our site your IP address is collected so that we know where to send information you are requesting. An IP address is often associated with the place from which you enter the Internet like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your school, if you are on a school computer. This information is not personally identifiable. Puzzles.COM and ThinkFun sites use information collected through technology to make our sites more interesting and useful to you. We normally don't combine this type of information with personally identifiable information. However, we will combine this information with personally identifiable information to identify a visitor in order to enforce compliance with our house rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, or others.

|   
|  |   
|  What Are Cookies, and How Does Puzzles.COM/ThinkFun Use Them? |   
|  Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site sends to your computer while you are viewing the Web site. These pieces of information allow the Web site to remember important information that will make your use of that site more useful. Puzzles.COM, ThinkFun and other Internet companies use cookies for a variety of purposes. For instance, the Puzzle Mart uses cookies to remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many Puzzles.COM/ThinkFun features that make your Web experience more efficient -- like the features mentioned above -- and some of our services will not function properly.

|   
|  |   
|  How does Puzzles.COM use the personally identifiable information that has been collected? |   
|  Puzzles.COM uses personally identifiable information in a limited number of ways. We use the information to complete transactions. For instance, if you purchase an item at the Puzzle Mart, we use your information to process your order, or if you contact us for help we will use the information to contact you. We use information collected to send you PuzzleCLUB information, or to notify you of exciting new ThinkFun information, if you have chosen that option. We do not share this information with third parties beyond the need to ship items you have purchased. |   
|  |   
|  Do Puzzles.COM or ThinkFun share information with companies or other organizations? |   
|  You are one of the most valuable assets of our site. We aren't in the business of selling information about our visitors. We will only share your information in the following manner:

Companies That Are Standing In For Puzzles.COM/ThinkFun

Sometimes we hire companies to help us deliver products or services, like a shipping company that delivers a package. In those instances, we need to share your information with them. These companies are basically standing in for Puzzles.COM and ThinkFun, and they are allowed to use the information only to deliver the product or service.

Organizations That Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Guests and Our Sites

We will give out personal information as required by law, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena; to enforce our Terms of Service, or site or game rules; or to protect the safety and security of visitors and our site.

|   
|  |   
|  What choices do I have about Puzzles.COM and ThinkFun collecting, using, and sharing my information? |   
|  It is possible for you to use much of our site without giving us any personally identifiable information. When you do register with us or give us personally identifiable information, you will have an opportunity at the time we collect your information to limit e-mail communications from Puzzles.COM. You can request at any time that we not send future e-mail to you either by unsubscribing from the communication or by contacting us at [support@ThinkFun.com](mailto:support@ThinkFun.com). Also, as mentioned above, there are ways to limit the information collected through technology. |   
|  |   
|  What type of security do Puzzles.COM and ThinkFun provide? |   
|  The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our visitors is of utmost concern to us. Puzzles.COM and ThinkFun take technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps to protect all visitors' information. When you provide credit card information, we use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to protect it. |   
|  |   
|  How can I access my account information? |   
|  You can access the personally identifiable information you gave us during registration by contacting us via e-mail at [ support@ThinkFun.com](mailto:support@ThinkFun.com). Please include information in the e-mail that will help us identify your account so we can assist you with your inquiry or request. |   
|  |   
|  How do parents access information about their kids? |   
|  Puzzles.COM and ThinkFun will not collect information other than email addresses from children who are 12 and younger. You can review your child's personally identifiable information by contacting Customer Service by email at [support@ThinkFun.com](mailto:support@ThinkFun.com). You also have the right to have the child's email address deleted and refuse the further collection and use of their child's personal information by emailing this address. Please include information in the email that will help us identify your child's account so we can assist you with your inquiry or request. |   
|  |   
|  Whom do I contact with questions or concerns about this privacy policy? |   
|  If you need further assistance, please send an email with your questions or comments to [support@ThinkFun.com](mailto:support@ThinkFun.com) or write us at:

ThinkFun Inc.  
1321 Cameron Street  
Alexandria, VA 22314  
Attn: A. Barthello

You can also reach us by phone at 1-703-549-4999.

Also a list of people who may access your information in addition to A. Barthello is here.

|   
|  |   
|  *Puzzles.COM is owned and operated by ThinkFun Inc., Everybody plays. ThinkFun designs, manufactures and sells a wide range of thinking games, brainteaser puzzles and toys. |   
|  |   
|  |  Last Updated: January 2, 2009 | top |   
---|---|---  
|  |
